So hi everyone my name is Shubham Bhatnagar I am
from ICC Lode General Insurance so
we are participating in PM BVA for I
guess since Inception it 2016 onward right now we are
present in three states
Maharashtra Andhra Pradesh and Jharkhand so I am
attending this conference on crop
simulation modelling now it has been
a three day long three days
of extremely hectic activities lots of
hands on and hands on sessions
specifically the one part of it which essentially
means the yield estimation through the
use of technology that I think is a
wonderful step because primer it is adding
an
effort to the way yield estimation happens in
this country and moving forward as newer
technologies are coming up and you have got a lot
of tools to analyse the data
positively as not just from mass as an
insurance company but from other
stakeholders as well